The Angel is a action, drama, history film directed by Ariel Vromen.
True story of Ashraf Marwan, who was President Nasser's son-in-law and special adviser and confidant to his successor
Anwar Sadat - while simultaneously Israeli Intelligence's most precious asset of the 20th century.
Based on NYT bestselling book 'The Angel: The Egyptian
Spy Who Saved Israel' by Uri Bar-Joseph.
Ashraf Marwan, played by Marwan Kenzari.
Danny Ben Aroya, played by Toby Kebbell.
Diana Davis, played by Hannah Ware.
Gamal Abdel Nasser, played by Waleed Zuaiter.
Mona Marwan, played by Maisa Abd Elhadi.
Anwar Sadat, played by Sasson Gabai.
The Angel is an Israeli spy thriller film directed by Ariel Vromen and
starring Marwan Kenzari and Toby Kebbell among others.
It is an adaptation of the non-fiction book The Angel: The
Egyptian Spy Who Saved Israel written by Uri Bar-Joseph.
It is a fictional account of Ashraf Marwan, a high-ranking Egyptian official who became a
double agent for both countries and helped achieve peace between the two.
The film explores themes of egypt, israel, politics,
power politics, international intrigue.
The tone is emotional and intense.